{
    "subject": "resource/Paul_Dresser",
    "predicate": "property/restingPlace",
    "object": "resource/Chicago",
    "human_readable": "Paul Dresser's resting place is Chicago.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9223629832267761,
            "question": "Where is Paul Dresser's resting place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8395801782608032,
            "question": "Is there a memorial for Paul Dresser in Chicago?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7786006927490234,
            "question": "In Chicago, where is Paul Dresser buried?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6899298429489136,
            "question": "What is the significance of Chicago for Paul Dresser?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6709242463111877,
            "question": "What city is associated with Paul Dresser's final resting spot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6571393013000488,
            "question": "Did Paul Dresser die in Chicago?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6145287752151489,
            "question": "Is Paul Dresser buried in a cemetery in Chicago?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5646502375602722,
            "question": "Who was Paul Dresser?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34483495354652405,
            "question": "Can you find any information about Paul Dresser's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34462791681289673,
            "question": "Was Paul Dresser a famous person?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Paul Dresser's resting place is Chicago.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2480_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you find any information about Paul Dresser's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2480_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was Paul Dresser?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2480_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Paul Dresser buried in a cemetery in Chicago?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2480_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2480_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2480_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2480_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2480_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2480_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2480_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2480_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2480_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2480_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2480_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text doesn't mention where Paul Dresser is buried, only that he was born in Terre Haute, Indiana and a memorial exists there.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents do not provide any information about Paul Dresser's resting place. The provided texts focus on his birthplace, a song he composed, and memorials in his honor but do not mention where he is buried or interred."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Paul Dresser was born, lived, and composed most of his music in Indiana. There is no information indicating that he was ever buried or has a resting place in Chicago.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Numerous references mention his birth place, family history, and legacy tied to Terre Haute, Indiana. There are also mentions of memorials and recognition within Indiana.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "there is no mention of Paul Dresser's resting place being Chicago. The information provided only talks about his birthplace, a state song, and various tributes and landmarks dedicated to him, but does not mention his place of death or burial.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information provided does not mention Paul Dresser's resting place. Instead, it focuses on details about his birthplace, the state song he wrote, and tributes to him in Terre Haute, Indiana. There is no information suggesting or implying that he is buried in Chicago.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}